Guide to the Kenneth J.Arrow Papers, 1939-2009
Kenneth J.Arrow Papers, 1939-2011
- Politics and Activism Series, 1974-1994.
  - Arms Control Subseries
    - Economists Against the Arms Race, 1987-93
    - Economists Against the Arms Race, 1987-93, (5 folders) (Box 16)
      - Haiffa Conference, 1994
      - Notre Dame Conference ( The Basic Economics of Arms Reduction and A Note on the Peace Dividend and Reallocation of Knowledge Skills by Arrow), 1990-91
    - National Research Council (NRC)-Nuclear War Committee, 1987-93
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1982-85
  - Human Rights Subseries
    - Aurora Foundation, 1987
    - Baha'i in Iran, 1982-83
    - Chili, 1976-79
    - Committee for Concerned Scientists, 1981-87
    - Committee for International Academic Freedom, 1992
    - Dissidents, 1974-91
    - Dissidents- Ida Nudel, 1978-79
    - El Salvador and Central America, 1984-90
    - South Africa, 1988
  - UNESCO Subseries, 1970s, (3 folders)
  - UNESCO Subseries, (9 folders) (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Involvements Subseries
    - American Council for an Energy-Efficient Economy, 1982-87
    - Clean Air Statement by Nobel Laureates, 1989
    - Clinch River Nuclear Breeder Reactor, 1983
    - Clinton Campaign, 1992
    - Current Wisdom, 1988
    - Dartmouth Prospect, 1993
    - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1975-78
    - Democratic Study Group, 1983
    - Drash, 1987
    - Earth Day, 1990
    - Economic Conversion Center, 1993
    - Economic Security Seminar, 1991
    - Food and Disarmament International, 1981-87
    - Gore, Sen. Albert (Economics Lecture), 1990-91
    - Heritage of Mankind, 1980-91
    - Hillel, 1980-92
    - Institute for Civil Justice, 1980-87
    - NAACP Legal Defense Fund- DuPont Case, 1993
    - National Committee on American Foreign Policy, Inc., 1981
    - National Institute of Economics and Law, 1982-83
    - Nova Specs, 1987-89
    - Nuclear Reactor Correspondence, 1974
    - Oregon Discrimination Case, 1983
    - Planned Parenthood, 1982
    - Proposition 35-Balanced Budget Amendment, 1984
    - Public Interest Economics, 1981-85
    - Public Statements, 1985-94
    - Real Peace, 1988
- Correspondence and Personal Files Series, 1980s-1990s.
  Contains files on various individuals. While the series is characterized mostly by correspondence, some files are primarily correspondence with the person, while others are primarily correspondence about the person, such as letters of recommendation or tenure revues.
  RESTRICTED
  - A- Boorman (includes Maurice Allais,; Takeshi Amemiya, and Scott Boorman) (Box 18)
  - Boxer- Dasgupta (includes Noam Chomskey) (Box 19)
  - Dasgupta- Gibbons (includes Gerard Debreu,; Aaron Douglas,; Jacques Drze,; George Feiwel,; Paul Fischbeck,; Milton Friedman, and Victor Fuchs) (Box 20)
  - Ginsberg- Honkapohja (includes Beila Goldman,; Stephen J. Gould,; Jerry Green,; Frank Hahn,; Peter Hammond,; John Harsanyi, and Jack Hirschleifer) (Box 21)
  - Hotelling- Ledyard (includes Harold Hotelling,; Leonid Hurwicz,; Michael Intriligator,; Peter Kalman,; Allen Kneese,; John Krutilla,; Tjalling Koopmans,; David Kreps,; Mordecai Kurz, and Guy Laroque) (Box 22)
  - Liebenstein- McAllister (includes Alain Lewis and Mark Machina) (Box 23)
  - McCloskey- O'Reilly (includes Donald McCloskey,; Lionel McKenzie,; Jacob and Robert Marschak,; Andrew Mas-Colell,; Eric Maskin,; Paul Milgrom,; Herv Moulin,; Daniel Patrick Moynihan,; Roger Myerson,; Marc Nerlov, and Terance O'Reilley) (Box 24)
  - O'Reilly-Stan (includes Terance O'Reilly,; Prashant Parikh,; Roy Radner,; Sherwin Rosen, and Etyan Seshinski) (Box 25)
  - Starr-Z, Letters of Reference, Harvard Years-A-E (includes David Starret, and Ron Trosper) (Box 26)
  - Letters of Reference, Harvard Years-F-Z (Box 27)
- Notes, Papers, and Research Series, 1939-1994 (bulk 1972-1994).
  This series will likely be of most interest to scholars of Professor Arrow's contributions to economic theory. While, like the other series, the bulk of this series dates after 1970, it does include files from earlier periods. The Class Notes and Theses Subseries contains notes from his undergraduate courses at City College of New York and graduate courses at Columbia University, including notes from Professor H. Hotelling's course in Mathematical Economics and a penultimate draft of his Masters Thesis. It also includes notes on meteorology in preparation for his work in the Army Air Corps. A subseries on Notes and Papers by Arrow also contains earlier work. The most extensive files in this subseries include notes on optimization and decentralization, a National Science Foundation project on production functions, stability, and uncertainty.
  The rest of the series contains work dating after 1970. The Notes for papers by Arrow Subseries contains drafts and notes for specific papers. The Ongoing Grants Subseries contains several projects funded by the National Science Foundation and the Office of Naval Research. The Notes Subseries contains files of notes relating to various topics, but seemingly unconnected to any specific paper. The last subseries, Festschrift and papers in the history of economic thought, contains files on those activities.
  - Class Notes and Theses (City College of NY and Columbia) Subseries, 1939-1943 (Box 28)
    - 1939 (?) Philosophy Classes (Nature of Mathematics, Philosophy of Mathematics, Consistency of a Mathematical System)
    - 1939-40 Honors Essays (Quaternions and Mathematical Statistics)
    - 1940 (?) Educational Psychology (Mexican Civilization)
    - 1940 Masters Thesis (Stochastic Processes, under Harold Hotelling), drafts
    - 1940 (?) Economics of Social Insurance (Actuarial Basis of Unemployment Insurance) and Mathematical Economics (with Harold Hotelling)
    - 1940-41 Theory of Functions (Jordan Separation Theorem and Prime Number Theorem)
    - 1941-42 Current Types of Economic Theory
    - 1943 Meteorology
  - Notes, Papers by Arrow, and Papers by Others Subseries, 1950-1978
    - Allocation of Risk Bearing by Arrow
    - Arrow reprints ( Alternative Approaches to the Theory of Choice in Risk-Taking Situations, 1952, Uncertainty and the Welfare Economics of Medical Care, 1963, Comments on Dusenberry's The Portfolio Approach to the Demand for Money and Other Assets, 1963, Control in Large Organizations, 1964 )
    - Equilibrium optimality, 1960 and 1968
    - Equilibrium and uniqueness (includes correspondence with Frank Hahn)
    - The Firm in General Equilibrium Theory by Arrow, 1969
    - Granger, C.W.J.-reprints
    - Optimal growth in linear models, 1965
    - Optimal growth, 1965-67, 1974, 1978
    - Optimization and Decentralization, 1950-60
      (notes, including on marginal cost pricing, and convergence of the limiting form of the gradient method; correspondence with William Gorman and Leonid Hurwicz; paper by Morton Slater; paper by Arrow and Hurwicz, Decentralization and Computation and Resource Allocation; paper by Arrow Optimization, Decentralization, and Internal Pricing in Business Firms)
    - Production functions
      - NSF proposal, 1960-64
      - Chenery- Solow proposal (project on production functions), 1964-70
      - Bibliography, 1969
      - CES fits
      - Elasticities
      - Embodiment, 1962-66
      - Learning-by-doing (includes correspondence with Joan Robinson), 1962-68
      - Murata, 1966
      - NSF reporting, 1964-65
      - Non-neutral progress, 1968
      - Relations to growth models, 1968
      - Statistical methods, 1965
    - Recognizing the Maximum of a Sequence, by John Gilber and Frederick Mosteller, 1966
    - Stability I, 1950s and 1960s (Box 29)
      (includes notes; papers and drafts by R.W. Clower,; David Gale,; Takashi Negishi,; Trout Rader,; Stanley Reiter, and Robert Wilson; and paper by Arrow and Hurwicz, Some Remarks on the Equilibria of Economic Systems)
    - Stability II, 1950s and 1960s
      (includes notes; notes from Maurice Allais; correspondence with Hurwicz; papers by Herbert Scarf,; Frank Hahn,; Hahn and Negishi,; Lionel McKenzie,; Peter Newman; and paper Arrow and Hurwicz, Competitive Stability Under Weak Gross Substitutability)
    - Stability III, 1950s and 1960s
      (notes, including unique stable equilibrium with one inferior good;; lectures; correspondence with Hurwicz; papers by Clower,; Hahn,; Negishi)
    - Uncertainty I, 1960s
      (includes correspondence with G.O. Bierwag,; William Brainard,; Jacques Drze,; Lucien Foldes,; Alvin Klevorick, and others; draft by Arrow Optimal Allocation of Risk Bearing)
    - Uncertainty II, 1960s
      (drafts; paper by Arrow, Aspects of Theory of Risk Bearing)
    - Uncertainty III, 1960s
      (notes, including theory of flood control; paper by Henry Allen Latan)
    - Uncertainty IV, 1960s
      (paper by Arrow and Robert Lind Uncertainty and the Valuation of Public Investment Decisions)
    - Uncertainty V, 1960s
      (notes, including adverse selection; notes from Gerard Debreu and Leo Tornquist; lectures; drafts; paper by Richard Nelson)
  - Notes for papers by Arrow Subseries, 1973-1994
    - Collected Papers of Arrow
      - correspondence
      - head notes
      - pictures
    - The Demand for Information and the Distribution of Income, 1985-86
    - The Division of Labor in the Economy, The Polity, and Society
    - The Economics of 1984, 1984
    - Economic Science in the Future, 1990
    - Economic Theory of Organization
    - Energy
    - The Short View and the Long, 1985
    - Equilibrium in Economics, 1987-90
    - Excellence and Equity in Higher Education, 1990-93
    - General Economic Equilibrium, 1973
    - The Genesis of Dynamic Systems Governed by Metzler Matrices, 1976
    - Income Testing and Social Welfare
    - Informational Equivalence of Signals
    - Information and Economic Behavior, 1973
    - Innovation in Large and Small Firms
    - An Interview with Kenneth J.Arrow (by Jerry Kelly), 1986
    - Is the World Going Socialist?
    - The Limits of the Market in Resource Allocation (with Steven Shavell and Janet Yellen), 1976
    - Microeconomic Simulation Models
    - Comments
    - Neoclassical Theory and its Discontents, 1993-94
    - Notes on Expectations Equilibria in Bayesian Settings (with Jerry Green), 1973
    - On a Theorem of Arrow
    - Comment, 1974
    - Origins of the Impossibility Theorem, 1991
    - Optimal Pricing, Use, and Exploration of Uncertain Natural Resource Stocks (with Sheldon Chang), 1978
    - Proposed Reforms of the Economic System of Information and Decision in the USSR (with Edmund Phelps), 1990
    - A Production Function for the Repairman Problem (with David Levhari and Eytan Sheshinski), 1970
    - Rationality of Self and Others in an Economic System, 1986-88
    - Rate of Discount on Investments with Imperfect Capital Markets (notes from Martin Feldstein)
    - Search, Equilibrium, and Information (with Michael Rothschild), 1973
    - Social Choice and Multicriterion Decision-Making (with Herv Reynaud), 1987 (Box 30)
    - Spatial Allocation of Non-Educational Public Expenditure/Public Investment for Optimal Development
    - Technical Information, Returns to Scale, and the Existence of Competitive Equilibrium, 1985-86
    - Uncertainty in Energy Planning, 1979
    - Handbook of Mathematical Economics, 1976-79
    - Handbook Series, 1979-93 (Box 31)
  - Ongoing Grants Subseries, 1973-1992
    - National Science Foundation (NSF)
      - Unification of Comparative Statics and Comparative Dynamics in General Equilibrium Models (with Peter Kalman), 1974-77
      - Social Associations Under Varying Market Structures (with Mordecai Kurz), 1980
      - Economic Interaction under Bounded Rationality and Limited Memory, 1986-92
      - Intrafirm and Interfirm Information Flows, 1982-84
      - Technology Assessment and Risk Analysis (TARA), 1982-87
      - Imperfect Competition and Price Stability in Competitive Equilibrium (with Frank Hahn), 1987
      - Informational and Organizational Impacts on Productivity (with Paul David, et al.), 1987-91
      - Information as an Economic Commodity (with Kurz and Robert Aumann), 1990-91
      - Dynamic Pricing Policies: Dupoly Equilibrium and Information (with Eytan Sheshinski), 1989-93
    - Office of Naval Research (ONR), 1979-91
    - ONR (Box 32)
      - Mark Machina Article, 1983
      - Urban Institute, 1973-76
  - Notes Subseries, 1972-1985, undated
    - Articles- Kevin McCabe et al., Vernon Smith,; Daniel Kahneman,; Elliot Montroll,; Marcello de Cecco,; Partha Dasgupta and Joseph Stiglitz,; Seppo Honkopohja,; Michael Lovell
    - Classical Famine, 1983
    - Cournot Oligopoly, 1979
    - Decentralization
    - Decentralization II
    - Duopoly
    - Dynamic Monopoly Pricing
    - Dynamic Systems
    - The Economy of Israel, 1984
    - Energy, 1972-79, 1985
    - Excerpt from The Collected Mathematical Papers of Arthur Cayley
    - Inflation-Remarks by William Fellner and Alan Greenspan, 1974
    - Miscellaneous Notes
    - Nonlinear Metzler System
    - OPEC Pricing
    - Demand Reduction
    - Organization Theory Group
    - Permanent Income as Welfare
    - Racial Discrimination
    - Social Choice-Correspondence and Notes
    - Tax Reform
    - Technology Assessment
    - Value of Life
  - Festschrift and Papers on the History of Economics Subseries, 1970s to 1990s
    - Arrow, Kenneth-Festschrift
    - Beckman, Martin-Festschrift
    - Bergson, Abram-Festschrift
    - Black, Duncan-Festschrift
    - Borch, Karl-Festschrift
    - Ehrlich, Alexander-Festschrift
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth-Festschrift
    - Hahn, Frank-Festschrift
    - Harsanyi, John-Festschrift
    - Hotelling, Harold-Festschrift
    - Houthakker, Henk-Festschrift
    - Hurwicz, Leonid-Festschrift
    - Kantorovich, L.V.-Festschrift
    - Karlin, Sam-Festschrift
    - Krutilla, John-Festschrift
    - Lerner, Abba-Festschrift
    - Labini, Sylos-Festschrift
    - Lipinski, Edward-Festschrift
    - Reder, Mel-Festschrift
    - Robinson, Joan-Festschrift
    - Shubik, Martin-Festschrift
    - Suppes, Patrick-Festschrift
    - Vickrey, William-Volume of Collected Papers
    - Von Neumann, John-Festschrift
    - Keynes's Treatise on Probability
    - Klassiker der Nationalokonomie (Edgeworth's Ethics and Ricardo's Work as Viewed by Later Economists)
    - Marshak, Jacob-Portrait (Box 33)
    - Marshak Recollections
    - Thorstein Veblen as an Economic Theorist
- Stanford and Harvard Series, 1948-1994 (bulk 1970-1994).
  Includes committee, consulting, volunteer, and other work for his universities and their economics departments. It also includes lectures notes and reading materials for courses that Arrow has taught at Stanford and Harvard. It is comprised of the Stanford University Subseries, the Stanford Economics Department Subseries, the Stanford Course Material Subseries, the Harvard University and Economics Department Subseries, and the Harvard Course Material Subseries.
  - Stanford University Subseries (Box 33)
    - Alumni
      - 1985-87
      - Bakersfield, 1987
      - New York, 1983
    - Centennial Campaign, 1986-89
    - Entering Student Talk, 1983
    - Ethics and Society Postdoctoral Fellowship, 1986-92
    - Extradepartmental Education, 1984-85
    - Engineering Research Center Proposal, 1985
    - Faculty Report, 1983-84
    - Football Recruiting, 1990
    - Fundamental Standard (Stanford Speech Code), 1989
    - Gardner Fellowship, 1985-89
    - Ground Rent Task Force, 1985-89
    - Health and Safety Review, 1988-90 (Box 34)
    - Homeowners Governance, 1989
    - Hoover Institution, 1981-94, (2 folders)
    - Housing, 1981-83
    - Humanities Center, 1983-91
    - Humanities and Sciences Council, 1986
    - Mathematical Sciences Education, 1984-85
    - Medical Non-Tenure, 1986-87
    - Public Service Requirement, 1990
    - Reagan Library, 1986
    - Research Committee, 1992
    - Seltzer Endowed Book Fund, 1988
    - South Africa, 1986
    - Stanford Negotiations and Correspondence, 1974-79
    - Stanford Retreat, 1990
    - Stanford Senate, 1987-89
    - Stanford Senate, Western Culture Debate, 1985-88
    - Stanford Summer, 1979
    - Stanford University Project for Environmental Research (SUPER), 1990
    - TSEMI, 1991
  - Stanford, Department of Economics Subseries
    - Alternative Approaches Field, 1986-88
    - Building, 1991
    - Department Computer, 1988
    - Economics Department (Memos and Meetings), 1983-94
    - Environmental Economics Appointment, 1990-92
    - Japan Trade Studies, 1985
    - Job Market, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Operations Research, 1990-91
    - Political Economics, 1985-86
    - Population Studies
    - Visiting Scholars, 1986
  - Stanford Course Material Subseries
    - Economics 186/Philosophy 077: The Ethics of Social Decisions, 1992-93
    - Economics 282/Operations Research 363: Theory of Information and Organization, 1984-91
    - Economics 386/Operations Research 366: Interdisciplinary Seminar on Conflict Resolution, 1981-93
    - Economics 388/Operations Research 369: Interdisciplinary Seminar on Risk Management, 1981-91
    - Optimal Economics Growth, 1967
    - Statistics Examinations, 1948-66
  - Harvard University and Department of Economics Subseries
    - Audit, 1981
    - Board of Syndics
    - Department of Economics, 1974-77
    - Department of Economics, Macroeconomics Search, 1971
    - Department of Economics, Faculty Appointments, 1989-93
    - Faculty Council Elections, 1976
    - Harvard Move (negotiations and correspondence), 1966-67
    - Houses, 1970-74
    - International Studies Committee, 1976-77
    - Kirkland House, 1974-79
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-79
    - South Africa, 1979
    - Wells Prize, 1978
    - Women Hiring Practices, 1975
    - Harvard Overseers, 1986-91
  - Harvard Course Material Subseries
    - Economics 205
    - Price and Allocation Theory
    - Economics 215: The Theory of Competitive Equilibrium, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Economics 225: The Theory and Estimation of Production Functions, 1969
    - Economics 2010a, 1973
    - Liquidity Preference
- Miscellaneous Series, 1950-1993 (bulk 1970s-1993).
  Comprised of the Prizes, Awards, and Honors Subseries, which includes correspondence surrounding his Nobel Prize award of 1970; the Personal (Arrow) Files Subseries, which includes biographical material and interviews, real estate activities, security clearance, and other private files; the Business and Publishers Subseries, which includes reprint permissions and correspondence with publishers; and the Referee Reports, and Book, Grant, and Other Reviews Subseries, which includes reviews of papers, books, and grants.
  - Prizes, Awards, and Honors Subseries (Box 36)
    - Cambridge Honorary Degree, 1985
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1974-92
    - Graduate Faculties Alumni of Columbia University (GFA) award, 1982
    - International Award of the Indian Econometric Society, 1975
    - Jewish Hall of Fame, 1989
    - Neumann Theory Prize, 1986
    - Nobel Prize
      - Royal Academy of Sciences
      - speech, 1972
      - ceremonies, 1972
      - references to work and publications, 1972-73
      - Kuratorom and Nominations, 1982-92
      - nominations, 1972-78
      - nomination for Amartya Sen, 1986
      - nomination for W. Edwards Deming, 1991
      - Jubilee, 1991
      - contract symposium, 1988-90
    - American Nobel Anniversary Committee, 1990
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1986
    - Sigma Xi, 1982
    - Washington University honorary degree, 1989
  - Personal (Arrow) Files Subseries
    - Biographical material, 1968-72
    - Biographical sketch (includes photographs), 1975
    - German Television (interview), 1988-89
    - Long Ridge (real estate), 1978
    - Personal-miscellaneous, 1968-72
    - Personal security information, 1950
    - Townsend Harris Alumni Association, 1980-91
    - Who's Who in World Jewry, 1976-77
  - Business and Publishers Subseries
    - Abt Books, 1982-88
    - Arthur D. Little, 1973
    - Basil Blackwell, 1982-83
    - Book Permissions, 1987-88
    - Elsevier, 1973-74
    - Harvard Book-author permissions, 1982-84
    - Holden Day, 1969-79
    - Holden Day, 1969-1979 (continued) (Box 37)
    - Irwin, 1982-89
    - Italian Translation, 1985
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1978-89
    - Limits of Organization, 1983-88
    - Markham, 1963-70
    - North-Holland, 1975-88
    - Norton, 1973-74
    - Oxford University Press, 1990-93
    - Patent agreement and misc. contracts, 1979
    - Permissions, 1979-94
    - Popular papers, 1984
    - Princeton University Press, 1994
    - Resources for the Future, 1979-84
    - Routledge, 1989-92
    - Zygmunt Gebethner, 1975
  - Referee Reports, and Book, Grant, and Other Reviews Subseries
    - Referee reports, 1978-93, (3 folders)
    - Miscellaneous evaluations and reviews, 1980-85
    - Aizerman, M.A., and F.T. Aleskerov, Choice of Variants, 1985
    - Brenner, Harvey, The Effects of Health Care and Health Promotion on Health Status in the United States, 1989
    - Hahn, Frank, Risk, Information, and Quality Signals in Economic Theory, 1993
    - Myerson, Roger, Game Theory, 1991
    - Nozick, Robert, 1974
    - Partisan Review (correspondence), 1982
    - Thurow, Lester, Dangerous Currents, 1983
- Accession (1998-0297), 1989-1997, 2 Boxes
  This addition to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers consists of office files, chiefly correspondence and memoranda, the bulk of which document Arrow's involvement in public and academic affairs as well as economics between 1989 and 1997.
  Access Restrictions
  Certain items are RESTRICTED. Users must agree to not reveal any personally identifiable information about living people without Arrow's approval. Access to some correspondence can only be obtained with permission from Arrow.
  - Invitations Declined, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Berlin WBZ Lecture - March 1994
  - Brown for Governor
  - Catastrophic Risk, Oct. 21-22, 1994
  - CEPR Search
  - Dummett Review
  - Empirica
  - EPA Discount Rate
  - Fuchs Symposium
  - Fulbright - Arrow
  - IEA: Rationality Conference, Turin, 1993
  - INDECON
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change
  - International Center for Peace in the Middle East
  - Jerusalem Summer School 1995
  - Jerusalem Summer School 1996
  - Jerusalem Summer Workshop 1994
  - MacArthur Economics Institute
  - Monash Increasing Returns Conference
  - NAPAP - National Acid Precipitation Assessment Progra m
  - National Oceanic Atmospheric Administration - Contingent Valuation
  - National Research Council - Report Review Committee
  - Nobel Democracy Symposium
  - Radin Review
  - Seltzer Lecture
  - SUNY Stonybrook
  - Uppsala Degrees
  - RESTRICTED MATERIALS
    - Chichilnisky vs. Wooders, (5 folders)
    - Chichilnisky vs. Wooders, (7 folders) (Box 2)
- Accession (2000-0222), 1977-1999, 2 Boxes
  The addition (2000-0222) (1,800 items, 3.0 linear ft.; dated 1977-1999) primarily contains professional correspondence and writings. The papers demonstrate Arrow's range of activities and responsibilities, especially as a speaker and conference attender. The addition also includes student and project files, including research conducted for the Office of Naval Research.
  This addition to the collection is RESTRICTED.
  - Rand Graduate School (Box 1)
  - P Correspondence
  - R Correspondence
  - Office of Naval Research Correspondence
  - N Correspondence
  - M Correspondence (1 of 2)
  - M Correspondence (2 of 2)
  - Correspondence K
  - Correspondence H
  - Hahn, Frank
  - National Research Council (NRC): Report Review Committee
  - COGEE
  - Croatia
  - Economic and Social Research Council (E.S.R.C.)
  - Journal of Economic Perspectives (JEP) discrimination
  - Lang, Serge
  - Correspondence D
  - L Correspondence
  - Education Department
  - Guttman Comment
  - Harvard Overseers
  - Hypothesis
  - Japan Development Bank Symposium, Fall 1995
  - Jerusalem, 1997
  - Chichilnisky-Wooders (1 of 2)